-[music]
-Even if women don't get to choose our
cue-2
members of Parliament, we're certainly
still involved in elections. Just take
cue-3
Lady Susan Keck. She's been campaigning
for the New Interest all over Oxfordshire,
cue-4
and there's many that say she'll win it
for them. I'm Fiddling Nan, known across
cue-5
these parts for my performances at fairs
and country dances. The New
cue-6
Interest have paid me and my band to raise
the cheer by playing and singing while
cue-7
people eat and drink their fill. For no
voter well can tell his side unless his
cue-8
belly's satisfied.
cue-9
They've given me a cockade to wear too,
made from orange ribbon, not like the blue
cue-10
ones worn by the Old Interest. But just
because I'm paid to be here and the
cue-11
cockade's a gift, that doesn't mean my
heart's not in it. Far from it. Just like
cue-12
good Lady Sue, I'm New Interest through
and through. Now, here's a good new song
cue-13
set to a good old tune. [music]
cue-14
My friends all attend, and I'll sing you a
song. The truth you shall hear, and I'll
cue-15
not keep you long. A meeting of gentlemen
so brave and bold. Some of the New
cue-16
Interest and some of the old. Derry down,
down, down, Derry,
cue-17
down.